[{"answer": "I mean the problem is that the good ones know they're good. And they know they're in such demand they're just not interested in confining themselves to one person", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Is my friend one of the good ones", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I hate the good ones", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "That's a good question, I think he thinks he is", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Who says I'm not bitter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, you can be young and bitter, just maybe not as bitter as I'm gonna be ten years from now, but I'm bitter. Anyway, don't tell anyone", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So what'd you do last night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Went out with my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Who is he", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "She's my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "So what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't know, what's with the eyebrows", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No! I'm not gonna do that! That's one step away from personal ads! And prostitutes! No! No, I am not going down that road! What does she look like", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How good looking", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "She's good looking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Very good looking", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "How good looking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Really good looking", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Very good looking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Really very good looking", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Really very good looking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes, I would take her out", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Good body, nice body", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Nice", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "How nice", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Just nice", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Nice", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Pretty nice", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Pretty nice", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Really very nice and good", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "First of all, what does he do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "He's not working?! How come he's not working", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "He's not working?! How come he's not working", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Why did he get fired", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You know, long dark hair", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Flowing", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Flowing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "'Thick lustrous hair is very important to me,' is that what you said", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Just clarifying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Do you want to be able to get it out or do you want to not be able to get it out", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Let me ask you this. If you stick your hand in the hair is it easy to get it out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'd like to be able to get it out", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Do you want to be able to get it out or do you want to not be able to get it out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I think you'll get it out", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "She's got a fine cheek", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "A pinkish hue", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I think it's tamber", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I didn't notice the voice", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Wait, I got another call. That must be him.  Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Oh, hold on.  It's my friend, he just got home", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I'm locking the vault. What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Oh my god, you had sex, how did that happen", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yeah, ok.  Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "What did he have to say", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "So, what did she have to say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "He said they had a good time", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I left three messages. I can't believe this woman. She has sex with me, leaves ten minutes later then I never hear from her again. What kind of a person does this? I mean, she used me. I feel cheap and violated", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "What are you gonna do", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I keep wracking my brain to try and figure out what I did. I was smart, I was funny, I made great small talk with the waitress so she could see I could relate to the commoners, you know, I'm a man of the people", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No, don't call her", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I'm gonna call her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "No, I'm calling her", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "No, don't call her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "No, my friend, don't call", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "No, I'm calling her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "No, forget it, I'm gonna call", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "No, my friend, don't call", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I don't want you to call", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "No, forget it, I'm gonna call", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Get away from me, I'm gonna call her", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Defective", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Who are you to talk about her like that? She'll call him when she's good and ready. You don't even know her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Her type? What type", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "I thought you said they had a good time, is there anything else you're keeping from me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "I'm calling you one if you are one, are you a liar", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Are you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fix-Up.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "You get yours out, I was here first", "qsentId": 78}]